(Siri:)Seven of them are fairly close to you.
(Raj:)Thank you, darling.
You're most certainly welcome, sexy.
- Well done, Dr. Koothrappali.
- I'm sorry?
(Sheldon:)You've taken
a great evolutionary leap...
(Sheldon:)...by abandoning human interaction
and allowing yourseIf...
(Sheldon:)...to romantically bond
with a soulless machine.
(Sheldon:)Kudos.
(Raj:)I haven't bonded with it.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, of course. I understand.
(Sheldon:)You're afraid the world isn't ready
for your taboo love.
(Sheldon:)Your secret's safe with me.
It's just a phone.
(Sheldon:)Cooper.
(Sheldon:)Kripke.
(Barry:)Heads up.
Professor Rothman urinated
in the particle physics lab again...
...so we're gonna move up
his retirement party.